<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Programming Guide on RFP-iOS-SDK Docs</title>
    <link>https://fout.github.io/RFP-iOS-SDK/en/programming-guide/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Programming Guide on RFP-iOS-SDK Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ja</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://fout.github.io/RFP-iOS-SDK/en/programming-guide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://fout.github.io/RFP-iOS-SDK/en/programming-guide/2_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fout.github.io/RFP-iOS-SDK/en/programming-guide/2_1/</guid>
      <description>Acquiring the Media Id Initialization within the code  This guide summarizes SDK usage.
For the detailed API specification, see the comments in each header file within the framework.

Acquisition of Media Id Register from the management screen to issue the Media Id.
(At the current stage, inquiries should be made to the representative)
This Media ID uses the app identification, so be sure not to forget this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acquisition of advertising framework Id</title>
      <link>https://fout.github.io/RFP-iOS-SDK/en/programming-guide/2_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fout.github.io/RFP-iOS-SDK/en/programming-guide/2_2/</guid>
      <description>Currently, you should contact our representative regarding advertisement framework registration settings.
The advertisement framework ID is issued from the management screen. When the following information is set, the advertisement framework ID is output.
 Advertisement framework name Advertisement image size
 Advertisement format(necessary only for simple In-Feed advertisements described later)
 Number of advertisement cases
 Advertisement position array
 HTML, width, height (necessary only when selecting the format to depict on WebView)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple infeed advertising</title>
      <link>https://fout.github.io/RFP-iOS-SDK/en/programming-guide/2_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fout.github.io/RFP-iOS-SDK/en/programming-guide/2_3/</guid>
      <description>Simple In-Feed advertisement display Acquiring events when displaying simple In-Feed advertisements Additional loading of simple In-Feed advertisements Simple In-Feed advertisement format Points to note when using simple In-Feed advertisements  A precondition for simple In-Feedadvertisements is use of UITableView.
For other uses, use Customized In-Feed advertisements.

Displaying simple In-Feed advertisements Here is an implementation example of simple In-Feed advertisement.
class YourViewController: UITableViewController, RFPInstreamAdLoaderDelegate { let adSpotId = &amp;quot;your_adspot_id&amp;quot; let adPositions = [3, 5] let instreamAdLoader = RFPInstreamAdLoader.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customized In-Feed advertising</title>
      <link>https://fout.github.io/RFP-iOS-SDK/en/programming-guide/2_4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fout.github.io/RFP-iOS-SDK/en/programming-guide/2_4/</guid>
      <description>Loading customized In-Feed advertisements Displaying customized In-Feed advertisements Notifying impressions of customized In-Feed advertisements Transition processing when clicking customized In-Feed advertisements Acquiring display characters for customized In-Feed advertisement button Loading customized In-Feed advertisements and acquiring events at the time of each notification Customized In-Feed advertisement parameters Arbitrary use of advertisement formats provided as default by SDK Acquiring exceptions occurring within SDK  When you want to display with more flexibility than with simple In-Feed advertisements, you can use customized In-Feed advertisement functions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Support for video advertising</title>
      <link>https://fout.github.io/RFP-iOS-SDK/en/programming-guide/2_5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fout.github.io/RFP-iOS-SDK/en/programming-guide/2_5/</guid>
      <description>※ Currently video advertisements can only be used by limited partners
 Components provided in the video advertising SDK Video advertisement judgment Used with video advertising Delegate method Acquiring video advertisements Playback preparation complete Playing videos Setting the cache  
Components provided with the video advertisement SDK  RFPPlayerControl  This is the UI view displaying the video player. This provides a function to control the video. Insert any UIView as a Subview.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Set HTTP request timeout interval</title>
      <link>https://fout.github.io/RFP-iOS-SDK/en/programming-guide/2_6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fout.github.io/RFP-iOS-SDK/en/programming-guide/2_6/</guid>
      <description>Set HTTP request timeout interval  
Set HTTP request timeout interval (Can be used on v2.6.0 or later)
Your app can use the RFP.rfpSetHttpRequestTimeoutInterval(_:) to set HTTP request&amp;rsquo;s timeout interval in RFP.
func application(_ application: UIApplication, didFinishLaunchingWithOptions launchOptions: [UIApplicationLaunchOptionsKey: Any]?) -&amp;gt; Bool { // Set HTTP request interval to 15s RFP.rfpSetHttpRequestTimeoutInterval(15) // ※ Be sure to set the rfpSetHttpRequestTimeoutInterval before rfpInitMedia RFP.rfpInitMedia(&amp;quot;your_media_id&amp;quot;) // Acquire current setting value let timeoutInterval = RFP.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>